lightbot.com 2015-05-19

# Lightbot Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

## Lightbot App

### Personal Information Collected

The Lightbot app does not collect any of the following: Email Address, Mobile Device Telephone Number, Photos/Videos, Browser History, Phone/Text Log, Contacts, Messages, Installed Apps, Location Data, Fingerprint Readings, Voice Authentication, or Health, Medical, or Therapy Data.

## Lightbot Website (lightbot.com)

### Personal Information Collected

The lightbot.com website does not collect any of the following: Mobile Device Telephone Number, Photos/Videos, Browser History, Phone/Text Log, Contacts, Messages, Installed Apps, Fingerprint Readings, Voice Authentication, or Health, Medical, or Therapy Data.

Lightbot.com may only collect an Email Address at http://lightbot.com/alpha.html solely for the purpose of outbound notification for when a new app is available to play.

Lightbot.com may also collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system, location data and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

### Operators collecting Data

### [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

The only cookies in use on our site are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it.

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page.

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page : https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

### Parental Rights

Lightbot is aimed at people both under 13 years of age and over.

Lightbot, both the app and website, does not require a child to disclose any information to participate or use the service, and furthermore, does not collect any personal or identifying information beyond what is stated above. No personal information is saved, and so parents can be assured that their child’s information is not collected. If parents wish to opt out of Google Analytics data collection, they may do so at the page https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. If a parent wants to have their child’s email address removed from the Alpha signup page at http://lightbot.com/alpha.html they may do so by contacting [contact.lightbot@gmail.com](mailto:contact.lightbot@gmail.com).

Lightbot is COPPA compliant.
